The call was the register to meet my city council for Monday November 18th, 2024.
Public input on schedule personal passes have none three claims list?
4 minutes from October 21st 2020 four regular meeting
So, I have several bars on my phone.
Hi!
Five, five, well-carrying on submission of grant application to United States Department
and the Agriculture for The Royal Development Community Facility Lone
in Grant to purchase equipment we just need
To type another up as a public meeting
If you've been questions about this
Anybody from any question?
You closed it with me
Are there any other questions?
We've got a question for the public hearing portion
and we want number six.
Resolution CC 2024 dash 13
And USDA rule development community facilities loan
Grant application agreement
The documents Melissa has ready
For you to sign there
This is completing
A grant award that
The USDA for equipment that we purchase
For vehicles and community development
We have got those,
Asking of reimbursement
This is the final paperwork
That has to be done so
Be re-inversed
To our 35%
Marker
Jim
Five
Award RFQ2488
Professional Services
Roadway Granted Improvement
Design Phase 1, FEMA
ER4500
Okay project 14
Oh, I can do it
Five
Eight
Remove issued weapon and badge for retiring employee Thomas Anderson
Keep in
Yes sir, requesting that
Is badge to get in retire with him
And take it off for our report
Question number two
Two full-time
Jones I've heard five
Five
Twenty four twenty five
PLA digital literacy
Work shop initiative grant
In the amount of $5000
Hello everyone so yes
We have we are
You've been awarded the $5000 so
Just need a approval for signing and moving forward with
The so our main focus will be cybersecurity
And internet basics
Focusing on general public
Signure citizens persons
With learning disabilities and teens
Really empowering you know whether it
Be senior citizen being able to navigate technology
And teen's learning cybersecurity as well
Being able
to get in our super excited
It's a very competitive grant
Motion different
Second
Hi
10 annual contract rule
From all concrete repair services
203-58
And I'm emotionally improve
All those with
Periper
Jones
And 11-12
We're on table
Motion of dollars or just
11 contract rule
From knowing and bailing
Public property C22-03
With Richard Wilson
This is for
They grant
For 2,500
Allers annually
It includes all the addresses
Can you guys see those in your packet there
These addresses
Richard Wilson represents
Mark 51 ranches one of the bid
On April 4th, 2022
He proposed to pay 2500 annually for
The city and
Right-to-Mowen bail
They have four extensions
Which would come
To a total of 12500
If all
We're asking for your approval to do the
Addendum again
And we have sign contract
I'll take it
Hi
We are taking
Except for reject RFP24-7
Fixed based operator services at
The Monter Regional Airport
First, you give a little recap of how
How
We have a report
On October 8, we opened those beds
Received three bids
Which was as frosty
That's the interest in their court
We reviewed them
Internally on November 15
Resent it into
The airport authority
On September 21
We had additional meetings with the airport authority
And then on today's meeting
With your affordability, they recommended that we reject all bids
At this current time
Let us get to New Terma Lopen
Let us see how staff progress is over
The next few months
On May 2, 2022
I'm like a motion
That way you will be rejected
Resent it into the 224-14
Created Senior Center at Biosery Board
And establishing an effective date
So council members, this is
Actually
The next three items
1560 and 17
Draw and applying with each other
Specifically on
The Biosery Board for the Senior Citizens Center
It would have five members that will be selected by the council
As far as other boards
Doesn't authorize them
Any authority to approve contracts or a necessary thing
To, For then
Be public access
For you, by as
You steps that they think would be necessary
And appropriate to approve the operations of
The Senior Citizens Center
But next item will actually
Approved five people
That'll serve on this board
Following items
This set up
We have here at
At a senior citizen center
Currently
There's benefit to the city
To keep that corporation in place
All of
Members and Board directors have resigned
And so there is no board for
That operation at this point
But on Friday
This Friday
The membership
Of
The Senior Citizens Center
Is having a meeting
To introduce amendments to their bylaws
And in those amendments
It calls for the board of directors
Be designated
By a city council
So, A slate
Who happens be
The same five people that are going
On this Board
We'll propose
For their 501c3
So it's somewhat similar to the city council
Serves in one capacity
But same five people
Serve
In
The same concept
We're using two different entities
Of
Our serving
And I believe five of these individuals have agreed
Like you right Mark and on there
That's correct
One of the same persons
They'd be a married
As for
You, both
Sure
I do
All right
I
The Senior Citizens
Carl and Carlin Calch
Cathy Wright and Eldon Johnson
Second
Farms
Consideration
For the Board of Directors
Of
The Minor Seniors Center
Carol Underhill, Carmen Couch
Kathy Wright
Discussion
The Board
I know the Mr. Carter
We've previously reached out to the
Lesson i
He had a $1400 invoice for
For the Fancy Funds
To talk about it
Asking on how
When overall
Just in discussion
Just thinking about the Board
We were talking
About everybody's community engagement funds
And said okay, we'll put five or six hundred dollars
For board member
Towards this you know to give him $3000
To kind of split
I mean what he thinks
He came out
Hello
I think
He's a little bit more
A lot of people can come because there was not
There wasn't lots of expenses
Maybe they'll be an opportunity to figure that out between them
Yeah, you know
We rented up piece
Of equipment for it and then we have about five thousand dollars
And expenses
Just pay real expensive
I feel like my ass saying
These are community engagement funds
So each board member gets $2,500
Except for the mayor and
The Mayor get 10000
How about you all to just pay four
I make a motion
We would want
To point out that we have not seen
Paperwork
That really verifies this but
Taking them at his work
Yeah
But is it going
And the engagement is going forward next year
If we can have more information
We'll be able to work on a tour
I had time like, will you?
Well think that actually did
For the most part
A little bit of time
Yeah
You know
No it's monster
Yep
How much do
I was saying it just in 3
Totally
5 people 600 bucks a piece
That's fine
All make emotion
Which we don't really have
Yeah, this is
Just put on as a discussion
How can you know
We cannot go
But
Really
You do not need to bring back the board if
That's okay
Your discretion
It was just a suggestion
Not to get us
Time too
I think you're got Brian
We talked about it
Yeah, right
You know the new business
Which is responsible for this agenda
20 staff reports
21 mayor council community in the council
Just want to say thank
I mean she has done an outstanding job
I mean
It's kind of hard
But us getting as many grants
We've gotten this year
And it is a great
With your team
You guys are doing
Thank you
There we go
Here
No, just to echo what
Offline
What he said
I know that from a community member's perspective
Thank you guys
From the board members' perspective
Way to go
This is awesome
Very, very proud
You're proud of me
A resident in my own, make sure proud
To be on this Board
Can't have for reason why we need
Make these decisions easier
Why do they give us?
Just keep up good work
It's all through the citizens
And they've been from it so to be able
We also had
The marketplace downtown
How do you market?
Another big success
Jimmy, did I have a big tunnel out of that one
Everybody sell out
So has live reindeer
Which was given
Back
The shirts are selling well
I heard that one
And the one you were worried about
Think it out there by his order
She had to make another one
Hey, the mayor's wife didn't even like
That shirt
But we'll find a way
We've got a nice one
If he went downtown
I don't know who's staff to think
Other than all of you
For the decorations downtown
They look freaking awesome
Some that lit up at night
And they looked right
So appreciate it, our work he has did
Everybody is crazy
But looks really good
You pulled away from other things
We appreciated
There was more to come
Almost getting a look like old time I
It is
You still not
Twenty first
I didn't think that
But Christmas break coming up to December 7
So if you want something in
Get it in
Have the floor to pray
Or your candy
You're not supposed to look in here
But anyway, the pray is coming up
We've got a tree lighting going on by yourself
I'll let Tyler, thank you for your work
So all of my thoughts
And now we will go city managers
The Christmas tree arrives
What's when?
When was that time as the lighting line
So I heard we have dancers, carolers
And some scared even ask
It'll be good
There's a lot of working parts in the downtown
Look and act the way it does
We will set our tree
Put on the green background
Follow out because there is travel
The long ways to get here
Pick up tomorrow
Let us know
We'll talk to the driver
Get pictures of dates and everything
Some day there is something we can get
Like another six in a picture
And then it's like I want
Everybody here
Help on these grants
The last one, obviously
Call them air
I said have to go after
Can you help me?
You know, volume and I put everything together
Talk to Derek and Glenn
And we got a day in it
It's matching grant but six million
The funds that are coming
This money is not here
So i wanted the bus out my shirt
We were in our grandstand
That was cool
What did you do?
Well this one makes him look thinner
We have never lost the day
I think we had four grants
That were on this agenda
So i mean staff is working very hard to bring me some money
Guys, what are you doing?
There's more of a work done that
Coming down in the park
And she says it has 4 more ready
It was not over
They're killing them
Real quick
We also have a window decorating competition going on
So you still sign up
I think this year they made it deal with the chamber
To where more businesses
Because of mainstream program and all these mainstream business
They partnered them to chambers
On the chambers, along down Main Street
You'll see more, i will lay out in that main street
Me interesting to say
Turnsout everybody involved
Okay
I'll tell him about 23
This meeting will now be continued
From the Calz chambers